

0821 1370 5067



Fatan Aminullah



PERSONAL

Birthday 15th June 2000 Relationship Single

: Indonesian Nationality : Bahasa, English Languages

SKILLS

- HTML
- MySQL
- CSS
- MongoDB
- Javascript
- Java Android
- Reactls
- React Native
- Nodels

CERTIFICATION

- UX Concept by Brainbench
- Certificate of Graduation by Purwadhika Startup and Coding School
- CCNAv7: Introduction to Networks
- Oracle Developer 12c by Brainbench

FATAN AMINULLAH

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

I am twenty years old, highly responsible of doing tasks, hard worker and fast learner type person. I am able to use English both written and oral and computer literate. I posses a strong will to learn much more in order to achieve high levels of performance. Capable for working on individually and team work.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer 2020 - Present

PT Emporia Digital Raya

- IKI Mitra Mobile Apps
- IKI Aku Mobile Apps
- IKI Bill Dashboard Website
- Uniqr QRIS Dasboard Website
- Report Dashboard Website

Frontend Developer 2019 - 2020

PT Anabatic Technologies Tbk

- Pocketbank Mobile Agent
- Pocketbank Mobile Customer
- Pocketbank Portal Web Admin
- Transaction Processing Engine (TPE) Web Funding
- Transaction Processing Engine (TPE) Web Teller
- Portal Web Multitenant

EDUCATION

Mercubuana University

2020 - Present

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

- database system
- programming
- mathematical logic
- business and management
- management of information system

Purwadhika Startup and **Coding School** 2019

WEB & MOBILE DEVELOPMENT

- programming fundamental with JavaScript
- frontend development or client side with react is
- backend development or server side with nodels and
- mobile development with react native

Nordic School of

JAVA ANDROID FUNDAMENTAL

- programming fundamental with java programming language
- OOP (object oriented programming)
- android software development

HOBBIES

Technology

2018









